http://www.radiantsolutions.com/privacy_policy

Privacy Policy
MAXAR TECHNOLOGIES INC. ("MAXAR")
This privacy policy (this "Policy") applies to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information by Maxar including personal information obtained through your use of Maxar’s website (the “Website”). This Policy does not apply to any of Maxar’s operating entities, each of which maintains their own privacy policies which are available on their websites. For the purposes of this Policy, “personal information” means information about an identifiable individual, but does not include statistical or aggregated information, or business contact information that Maxar uses solely for the purpose of communicating or facilitating communication with you in relation to your employment, business or profession.
We may update this Policy from time to time and will post any revisions in the form of an updated Policy. Any personal information you submit to us will be governed by the Policy in place at the time of submission.
Our Commitment
We are committed to protecting personal information in our control and have developed and implemented policies and procedures for the proper collection, use and disclosure of personal information.
Electronic Personal Information
We may use cookies on the Website. "Cookies" are small text files that recognize repeat visitors and track their visits to the Website. Specific browser manufacturers or providers should be consulted with respect to disabling cookies.
We may use clear gifs. "Clear gifs" are used to track the pages visited on the Website to help us improve the design and content of the Website. All of this information is considered confidential and is only available for our use.
We may monitor traffic patterns, Website usage and related Website information in order to optimize the Website.
Collection, Use, Disclosure and Retention
We will only use or disclose personal information for the specific purpose(s) for which it was collected, except with your consent or as required or permitted by law. Any personal information you provide to us may be shared and used by our subsidiaries and other service providers solely for this purpose.
We will retain personal information only as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes stated above, as required for legal or business purposes or as required by law. Subsequently, we will destroy, erase, or make anonymous such information.
We take reasonable precautions to ensure the protection of personal information, collected, used or disclosed by us using appropriate physical, organizational and technological measures.
Questions/Concerns
If you have any questions or concerns with our privacy practices and/or this Policy or wish to access any personal information you have provided to us, please email us here.
International Transfer and Storage of Information
Maxar is a global organization and maintains and otherwise uses servers and hardware located throughout the world. Personal information you provide may be maintained on any such hardware or the hardware of our service providers whose assets are located across the globe. We will use reasonable means to ensure that personal information is protected regardless of where your personal information may be located.
